<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aegisub Options</title><link>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/miscellaneous/options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/miscellaneous/options/</guid><description>Aegisub is highly customizable and hence has a large amount of user-changeable options. These are available in the options dialog box, found in the View menu. This page is a reference of all the available options.
Aegisub stores all its configuration in a plain text file called config.json which by default is stored in the [[?user|Aegisub_path_specifiers]] directory. If you want to reset Aegisub to its default options without reinstalling the program, you can just delete config.</description></item><item><title>Script Properties</title><link>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/miscellaneous/properties/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/miscellaneous/properties/</guid><description>The script properties are some headers and other options that affect the entire script in various ways. They can be accessed from the File menu -&amp;gt; Properties.
{: class=&amp;ldquo;center&amp;rdquo;}
The properties are:
Title, Original script, Translation, Editing, Timing, Synch point, Updated by and Update details - These are for informational purposes only and do not affect rendering in any way. Set them to appropriate values if you find them useful.</description></item><item><title>Attachment Manager</title><link>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/miscellaneous/attachment_manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/miscellaneous/attachment_manager/</guid><description>The attachment manager allows you to attach fonts and/or pictures to your script (by encoding them as text). This is occasionally useful for sharing fonts between everyone who is working on a script without having to send the fonts as separate files. However, it is quite limited and is prone to causing problems.
Overview The entire dialogue is fairly self-explanatory. The two &amp;ldquo;Attach &amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; buttons add attachments, &amp;ldquo;Extract&amp;rdquo; extracts existing attachments into separate files, and &amp;ldquo;Delete&amp;rdquo; deletes attachments from the subtitles file.</description></item><item><title>Main Page</title><link>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/main_page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aeg-dev.github.io/AegSite-hugo/docs/main_page/</guid><description>Welcome to the Aegisub manual. See our about page for more information on the program, or browse the topics on the left bar.
Documentation related to delopment of Aegisub and building Aegisub is located at the bug tracker.
Starting points [[Quick overview of Aegisub|Overview]]
Common tasks:
[[Timing a translated script to audio|Audio]] [[Basic typesetting of on-screen signs|Tutorials#visualtypesetting]] [[Putting your finished subtitles onto the video|Attaching_subtitles_to_video]] (for viewing or distribution) ^</description></item></channel></rss>